Curriculum Vitae
Rosie Buddell
31 Millfields Close
BR5 2LQ
07714779730
rosie.buddell@gmail.com
rosiebuddell.tumblr.com

About Me:

I am extremely hardworking and punctual

I have excellent communication skills, and I really enjoy meeting new people, and using my creative thinking.

I am currently a first-year student at Ravensbourne, studying Web Media.

I have 2 years experience in customer service, and keeping a level-head in stressful situations, and dealing with customer complaints.

Education:

Ravensbourne, Greenwich Peninsula
Attended: September 2015 to present
Straight A Training (apprenticeship), Southbank, London
Attended: September 2013 - May 2014
Canterbury College, Canterbury
Attended: September 2011- July 2013
Beaverwood School for girls, Chislehurst
Attended: September 2004- July 2011

Qualifications:

Subject	Grade
English, Maths, Science, French, Art, and History	All Grade C (GCSE)
ICT	B (GCSE)
Drama & Theatre, and English Literature	C (A Level)
Creative Media Production (Print, Radio & TV)	MMP (BTEC)
Business and Administration Level 3	Pass (NVQ)

Achievements:

Jul 2011 - Completed 7 years at secondary school with the qualifications as listed above, GCSE's and A Levels.

Jul 2013 - Completed 2 years at College, with a MMP grade in Creative Media Production (BTEC)
Sept 2014 - Completed a year long apprenticeship at ITV Studios Global Entertainment in the Digital
Marketing and International research department

Work Experience:

Sept 2014 - Sept 2015 I joined the Insight and Research team at Sky Media UK, where I provided sales teams with pitches and customer insights to pass on to advertising agencies and clients. I left my position to study Web Media at university.

Sept 2013 - Sept 2014 I was an apprentice working in the Digital Marketing and International Research team for ITV Studios Global Entertainment. During my employment, alongside studying for an NVQ in Business and Administration, I learned the inner workings of a highly successful TV production company and got to work on key titles such as *Thunderbirds Are Go!* and *Mr Selfridge*, amongst others.

Nov 2011 - Jul 2013 I worked as a crew member for McDonalds, Stour Road Retail Park, Sturry. During my employment here I learned how to keep calm in stressful situations, how to deliver outstanding customer service, and always keep up an energetic and cheerful approach to each working day.

References Available on request